let questions=[ //mobile
{ numb : 1,
question:"Identify the language on which Android is based upon.",
answer:"Java",
options:[
"C++",
"Java",
"Python",
"None"
]
},
{ numb : 2,
question:"In android, mini activities are also known as",
answer:"Fragments",
options:[
"Fragments",
"Activity",
"Adapter",
"None"
]
},
{ numb : 3,
question:"Choose the option which is contained in the src folder",
answer:"Java source Code",
options:[
"Java source Code",
"Xml",
"Css",
"All"
]
},
{ numb :4 ,
question:"Identify the parent class of activity.",
answer:"contextThemeWrapper",
options:[
"contextThemeWrapper",
"Context",
"Object",
"None"
]
},
{ numb :5 ,
question:"Choose among the following tabs in which an error is shown",
answer:"Logcat",
options:[
"Logcat",
"Adb",
"Cpu",
"memory"
]
},
{ numb :6 ,
question:"When was Open Handset Alliance announced?",
answer:"2007",
options:[
"2004",
"2005",
"2006",
"2007"
]
},
{ numb : 7,
question:"Identify among the following which is not a state in the service lifecycle.",
answer:"Paused",
options:[
"Paused",
"Start",
"Destroyed ",
"Running"
]
},
{ numb : 8,
question:"Choose the built-in database of Android.",
answer:"SQLite",
options:[
"SQLite",
"MySQL",
"Oracle",
"none"
]
},
{ numb : 9,
question:"Identify the layout in which Android arranges its children into rows and columns.",
answer:"TableLayout",
options:[
"FrameLayout",
"RelativeLayout",
"TableLayout",
"None"
]
},
{ numb : 10,
question:"Choose the correct option to find the JSON element length in Android JSON.",
answer:"Length()",
options:[
"sum()",
"Length()",
"Count()",
"add()"
]
},
];